Welcome to this short course on LLM for Large Language Model Application Development.
欢迎参加这个关于大型语言模型应用开发的LLM短期课程。
By prompting an LLM or large language model, it is now possible to develop AI applications
通过提示LLM或大型语言模型，现在有可能开发人工智能应用程序
much faster than ever before.
比以前快得多。
But an application can require prompting an LLM multiple times and parsing its output,
但一个应用程序可能需要多次提示LLM并解析其输出、
and so there's a lot of glue code that needs to be written.
因此，有很多胶水代码需要编写。
LLM for Large Language Model Application Development, created by Harrison Chase, makes this development
由Harrison Chase创建的用于大型语言模型应用程序开发的LLM 使这一开发过程
process much easier.
变得更加容易。
I'm thrilled to have Harrison here, who had built this short course in collaboration with
我很高兴Harrison来到这里，他曾与其他的人合作建立了这个短期课程。
DeepLearning.ai to teach how to use this amazing tool.
DeepLearning.ai教你如何使用这个神奇的工具。
Thanks for having me.
谢谢你邀请我。
I'm really excited to be here.
我真的很高兴能在这里。
LangChain started as an open source framework for building LLM applications.
LangChain开始是一个用于构建LLM应用程序的开源框架。
It came about when I was talking to a bunch of folks in the field who were building more
它是在我与该领域的一群人交谈时产生的，这些人正在建立更多的
complex applications and saw some common abstractions in terms of how they were being developed.
复杂的应用程序，并在如何开发方面看到了一些共同的抽象概念。
And we've been really thrilled at the community adoption of LangChain so far, and so look
到目前为止，我们对LangChain的社区采用情况感到非常兴奋，所以看起来
forward to sharing it with everyone here and look forward to seeing what people build with
期待着与这里的每一个人分享，并期待着看到人们用它建造的东西。
it.
它。
And in fact, as a sign of LangChain's momentum, not only does it have numerous users, but
而事实上，作为LangChain势头的一个标志，它不仅拥有众多的用户，而且
there are also many hundreds of contributors to the open source.
也有成百上千的开放源码的贡献者。
And this has been instrumental for its rapid rate of development.
这对其快速的发展速度起到了重要作用。
This team really ships code and features at an amazing pace.
这个团队真的以惊人的速度交付代码和功能。
So hopefully after this short course, you'll be able to quickly put together some really
因此，希望在这个简短的课程之后，你将能够迅速地把一些真正的
cool applications using LangChain.
使用LangChain的很酷的应用程序。
And who knows, maybe you even decide to contribute back to the open source LangChain effort.
谁知道呢，也许你甚至决定回馈给开源的LangChain工作。
LangChain is an open source development framework for building LLM applications.
LangChain是一个用于构建LLM应用程序的开源开发框架。
We have two different packages, a Python one and a JavaScript one.
我们有两个不同的包，一个是Python包，一个是JavaScript包。
They're focused on composition and modularity.
他们专注于组成和模块化。
So they have a lot of individual components that can be used in conjunction with each
因此，他们有很多单独的组件，可以相互结合
other or by themselves.
或单独使用。
And so that's one of the key value adds.
因此，这是关键的附加值之一。
And then the other key value add is a bunch of different use cases.
然后其他关键的增值是一堆不同的使用案例。
So chains of ways of combining these modular components into more end-to-end applications
因此，将这些模块化组件组合成更多的端到端应用的方法链
and making it very easy to get started with those use cases.
并使开始使用这些用例变得非常容易。
In this class, we'll cover the common components of LangChain.
在这堂课中，我们将介绍LangChain的常见组件。
So we'll talk about models.
因此，我们要谈一谈模型。
We'll talk about prompts, which are how you get models to do useful and interesting things.
我们将谈论提示，这是你如何让模型做有用和有趣的事情。
We'll talk about indexes, which are ways of ingesting data so that you can combine it
我们将讨论索引，索引是引入数据的方法，以便您可以将其与模型组合在一起。
with models.
And then we'll talk about chains, which are more end-to-end use cases, along with agents,
然后，我们将讨论链，这是更多的端到端用例，同时还有代理、
which are a very exciting type of end-to-end use case, which uses the model as a reasoning
这是一种非常令人兴奋的端到端用例，它使用模型作为推理引擎。
engine.
We're also grateful to Ankush Gola, who is the co-founder of LangChain alongside
我们也很感谢 Ankush Gola，他和Harrison Chase都是是LangChain的联合创始人。
Harrison Chase, for also putting a lot of thought into these materials and helping with
他也对这些材料投入了大量的心血，
the creation of this short course.
并帮助创建了这个短期课程。
And on the deep learning, the AI side, Geoff Ladwig, Eddy Shyu, and Diala Ezzeddine have
在深度学习方面，人工智能方面，Geoff Ladwig, Eddy Shyu 和 Diala Ezzeddine
also contributed to these materials.
也为这些材料做出了贡献。
And so with that, let's go on to the next video where we'll learn about LangChain's
因此，让我们继续观看下一个视频，我们将了解LangChain的
models, prompts, and pauses.
模型、提示和停顿。